A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Affordable Health Insurance, SG 3, Series 11 FA1473
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Affordable Health Insurance, SG 3, Series 11
2007-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1473
1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter-size document boxes
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Scope and Contents
The Affordable Health Insurance series contains background information and reports of health care reform 2007-2009, including issue briefs, and analysis, comparisons, and drafts of congressional bills.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC in 2010 as accession 2010:047.
- Issue Brief - Oral Health, Dental Insurance and Access to Dental Care, 2008 March (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Issue Brief - Likely Cobra Eligibility, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Products from Biennial, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Failure to Protect - Why the Individual Insurance Market is Not a Viable Opion, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Individual Insurance (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Low Wage Workers Brief (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Medical Debt Issue Brief, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Biennial States Issue Brief - Women (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Administrative Costs Issue Brief, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 2009-2020 Premium Projections (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Billings, MT - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Albuquerque, NM - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Atlanta, GA - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Atlanta, GA - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Boise, ID - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Wyoming - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- North Carolina - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Bridgeport, CT - Coverage Quotes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Sara R. Collins - New York City Council Testimony, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 2008 Presidential Candidates Report (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Congressional Bills, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Issue Brief - After Hours Access, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Congressional Follow-Up - Calls (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Health Reform Bills Report Early Version, 2009 August (Box 3, Folder 24)
- College Plans - Beckley, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Congressional Bills Side by Sides and CBO, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Health Reform Bill, 2009 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Coverage Analytic Report, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Health Reform Bill - Long, 2009 Summer (Box 3, Folder 29)